Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
なんか嫌だ?
Did it tickle?
くすぐった?
Did your whole body tickle?
全身くすぐった?
It hasn't been developed yet.
まだ、そこは開発されてないのね
This is where it feels good.
気持ちいいところは、ここ
Kokoto?
ここと?
What else?
あとは?
Only here?
ここだけ?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
Doesn't it feel good to be licked so much?
もっぱい舐められるのが気持ちよくない?
It feels good.
気持ちいいもんね
It tickles my ears, and it tickles my back.
耳はくすぐったい、背中もくすぐったい
But it tickles and it feels good.
だけど、くすぐった気持ちいい
I won't do it because I feel tickled.
くすぐった気持ちだから、やらないよ、
Better do it.
やったほうがいい
Is that okay?
そういうことでいい?
That's fine.
そういうことでいい
Sasaki, please be honest.
佐々木、お正直言いなさい
Be honest.
正直言いなさい
why?
なぜ?
You were embarrassed because you leaked it earlier, right?
さっき漏れてみたから、恥ずかしかったでしょ?
You were embarrassed because you saw it when you took down your pants earlier, right?
さっきのパンツ下ろしたとき、見たから恥ずかしかったでしょ?
why?
な ぜ?
なぜ?
show me.
見せて
Show me.
見せてほら
show me.
見せて
Are you okay,
大丈夫、
Are you okay.
大丈夫
There's a mole on something.
何 かにほくろがあるのね
Yeah, yeah, don't say that.
うん、そう、言わないでよ
What is this? Is your hair shaved?
これ何、毛は剃ってたりしてるの?
Are you having a good summer?
なつもしてるの?
A lot of people are watching me.
なつもの人に見られてるじゃん
Are you wearing these pants and hiding them like this?
パンツ、ここ履いて、こう隠してるの?
So, what's going on here?
で、ここがバチバチバチってやるの?
Put on your pants and look from the side like this.
パンツを履いて、こうやって横から
Raise your hips.
上げて、腰上げて
a little bit.
ちょっと
Just a little bit.
ちょっと ね
You can spread it with your hands, right?
自分の手で広げるでしょ?
This side, both.
こっち側、両方
Spread it out.
広げて
Look, look.
見て、見て
Here, show me.
ほら、見せて
Look, look.
ほら、見て
You can see it, right?
見えるでしょ?
Look carefully.
よく見て
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
Look carefully.
よく見て
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
Oh no, that's naughty.
やだ、やらしいもんな
I won't let my boyfriend
彼氏に許さない
Right?
で しょ?
What?
え って
えって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Well then, show me.
じゃあ、見せて
Don't hide it.
隠さないで
Spread it out, spread it out for a while.
広げて、しばらく広げて
Show me well.
よく見せて
Yes, that's right.
はい、そう
Look.
見して
I want to see this, everyone.
見たいんだよ、これ、みんな
Look at it properly.
見して、ちゃんと
It came out, it came out.
出てきた、出てきた
Look, it's out.
ほら、出てきた
Wait, wait.
待って、待って
Ecchi.
えっちー
Spread it out a little.
ちょっと広げて
Look.
見して
It came out, right?
出てきたでしょ?
Something came out, right?
何か出てきたでしょ?
Properly.
ちゃんと
Look, it's out.
ほ ら、出てきた
why?
なんで?
Enough?
もういい?
Show me, show me.
見せて、見せて
Look, that's amazing.
ほら、すごい
Too shy.
恥ずかしいがりすぎる
It's not embarrassing at all.
全然、恥ずかしくないからね
But, An-chan.
でも、あんちゃん
Fourth.
4つ目
Push through.
押し抜けて
Push, push, push.
押す、押す、押す
That's fine.
そっちで、いいよ
Just push it up.
そのまま押し上げてね
Just like that.
そのまま
Just like that, Petan.
そのまま、ペタンって
Push it up flat.
ペタンって押し上げてね
Push it up.
押 し上げて
A mess.
ぐしゃぐしゃぐしゃ
It's shining, it's shining.
光ってる、光ってる
No more?
もうダメ?
Is it too embarrassing?
恥ずかしすぎてダメ?
Are you too embarrassed to do it?
恥ずかしすぎて無理ですか?
Push it up, push it out.
押し上げて、突き出して
Something like a mess.
ぐしゃぐしゃとか
what?
何?
I'm so embarrassed that I don't want to show it, or should I force it to be shown to me.
恥ずかしくて、見せらんとか押し見せてもらおうか
Why don't you show it to me yourself or let me show it to you?
自分で見せらんのか、俺が見せてもらおうか
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Look.
ほら
Dogs are small, aren't they?
ワンコ、ちっちゃいよね
That's amazing.
すごいね
This doesn't happen, right?
こんなことないでしょ
Small.
ちっちゃい
It's really small compared to its size.
体の割に、本当小ぶりなんだもん
Don't you like it anymore?
もう嫌だ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Hey, I want to see it.
ち っちゃ い、見たいんだわ、
everyone.
み んな
It's nostalgic.
懐かしいよさ
I could also see her butthole.
お尻の穴もこれ見えちゃった
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ
When did you poop?
うんち、いつしたの?
what?
何?
Open it, it'll smell.
開けて、匂うから
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ、嫌だ
It might smell like poop.
うんちの匂いするかも
I absolutely hate it.
絶対嫌だ
I understand, I understand.
分かった、分かった
I don't like it.
嫌だね
It seems so spacious.
広 が ら しいじゃん
It's going to spread.
広がっちゃうよ
It won't spread.
広がんないよ
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
Mischief.
いじわる
Put it on me
俺のせ
stomach.
い
Is it my fault?
俺 のせい?
俺のせい?
The thrill of the sword is amazing.
剣のゾクゾクがすごいじゃん
Oh my god, did you turn on the switch?
やばい、スイッチ入った?
Did you turn on the switch?
スイッチ入った?
what?
何?
I'm feeling kind of gutter.
なんかグターってなってるよ
Hey.
ねえ
That's naughty.
やらしいな
That's what I recommend.
それがおすすめですよ、それは
How many can you show me by yourself?
一人でして何個見せてよ
It's a shop.
お店なんだね
Well then, no.
じゃあ、いいや
I'll show you.
俺が見せてあげるよ
Hey, hey.
ちょっと、ちょっと
Because they don't show it to me at all.
全然見せてくれないから
I felt embarrassed.
恥ずかしくなって
Sit cross-legged here.
このあぐらの上に座って
On top.
上に
Okay.
よ いしょ
good?
いい?
I don't like it!
嫌!
It looks good like this, right?
こうやってよく見えるでしょ?
With your feet?
足で?
that?
それ?
I'll last a little longer.
もうちょっと持つで
I can go forward.
前に行ける
forward?
前?
That's right, it's going to fall.
そうそう、落ちちゃう
There's something so sneaky about recon.
リスコンなんなんこそこそがあって
Whatever it is.
なんであって
Are you going to make me look like this?
こんな格好させるの?
Yeah.
うん
Stop it.
やめ
Don't close it.
閉じないで
It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
すんのぶりきた
What are you saying?
なんて言ってんの?
tell me.
教えて
picture?
え?
What are you saying?
なんて言ってんの?
it hurts.
痛い
what?
なに?
why?
なんで?
You're saying hiccha hiccha.
ひっちゃひっちゃ言ってるね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
What do you think will happen?
どうなっちゃいそう?
tell me.
教えて
Have you gone crazy?
おかしくなっちゃった?
Is this how it ends?
こんなおしまい?
What happened when it ended?
おしまいってどうしちゃったの?
Don't stop, already.
やめんのね、もうね
Because I said it was over.
お しまいって言ったから
That's really mean.
すっごい意地悪だな
Don't stop, right?
やめんでしょ
It's over, isn't it?
おしまいでしょ、もう
Is it over?
おしまい?
Will it end?
おしまいする?
It's over.
おしまいって
おしまい
immediately.
すぐに
It's over.
おしまいしたんだ
おしまい
Why don't you leave?
お しま い しないの?
Are you used to seeing things like this in Shell?
シェルでこんな見慣れてんの?
Too pretty?
きれいすぎ?
No?
ダメ?
Too ticklish?
くすぐったすぎ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Well then, let's smoke it.
じゃあ、吸ってやこう
Isn't it funny?
おかしくね?
See you then.
じゃあね
What did you say?
なに言っちゃったの?
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした
Can I try it?
やってみていい?
It's hard to do it for the first time.
初めてやるの大変だよ
Get some sleep.
ちょっと寝てて
Sleep.
寝てて
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫大丈夫
Do you have it?
持 ってる?
can?
できる?
scared?
怖い?
You like toys.
おもちゃ好きなんだね
It's a toy.
おもちゃなんだ
What happened?
どうなった?
Too strong?
強すぎ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
With your fingers.
指でな
No more?
もうダメ?
You haven't gone yet, have you?
まだ行ってないよね?
went?
行 った?
Did you go?
行ったの?
You have to tell me.
教えなきゃダメだよ
I can't do it anymore.
もう無理だよ
It's melty.
とろっとろじゃん
Try touching it.
触ってみて
hot?
熱い?
Something more powerful.
もっと強力なやつをさ
Do you want to smoke this?
これ吸う?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Inhale this.
これ吸い込んで
I'm inhaling, inhaling, choo choo.
吸い込んで吸い込んで、チューチューしてる
It's real.
リアルシイね
I'm choo choo choo.
これチューチューチューしてるよ
Tell me you're going when you go.
行くとき行くって教えて
what up?
どうした?
Are you sweating?
汗だくなっちゃった?
hot?
熱い?
Shall we take a break?
休憩する?
You slept for a while.
ちょっと寝てたね
Shall we take a break?
休憩する?
Don't want to take a break?
休憩するの嫌だ?
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
Don't sweat.
汗こらないでよ
You'll start sweating right away.
すぐに湧き汗もすぐに
Tell me, tell me, tell me.
教えて教えて教えて
No?
ダメ?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
You're doing it just like that.
そのままやってるじゃん
I'll definitely go again.
ちゃんとまた行くんだよ
The sound of sucking.
吸う音
That's nice.
いいな
Keep going.
続け続け
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫大丈夫
I'm not scared, I'm not scared, I'm not scared.
怖くない怖くない怖くない
A real sucking sound.
ほんと吸う音
Sun
すん
You're safe, aren't you?
ご い無事でしょ